Graves, Rhoda Fox; Papers apap364
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Senate Files, 1914-1948; 2; 7.2 cubic ft.
  - Legislative Service, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Liquor, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Malone, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Minutes of Hearing of Joint Leg. Committee on Home Rule for Villages, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Nursing Bill, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Price Fixing Bill (1 of 2), 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Price Fixing Bill (2 of 2), 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - R--Acknowledgement and Requests for Red Book and Manuals, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Releases, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Resolutions, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - S--Correspondence, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Waterways, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - World's Poultry Congress, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Saranac Lake, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Cray, Edwards D., 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Deferred Auto Registration and Other Correspondence, 1939; Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Assemblymen, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Bulletin: Friends of the Public Schools Newsletters, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Florida, 1939-1941; Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Berghold and Dillon, 1939-1941; 1943 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Fine--Fowler, 1939-1941; 1943; Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Invitations, 1939-1942 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Hard of Hearing Committee, 1939-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1939-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Handwritten Senate Notes and Supplemental Material, 1939-1943 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    May be connected to folder titled "Investigation"
  - Education, 1939-1943; Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Potsdam, 1939-1943; Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Red School House, 1939; 1942 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Oswegatchie, 1939; 1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Legislation on Dairy Industry, 1939; 1941 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Cooperative Corporations Bill (Also Inspection), 1939; 1944; Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lane Bryant, 1939; 1946; Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - London, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Plattsburgh, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Willkie Letter--Election, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Worlds Fair-- Women, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Bureau of Government Research, 1940; Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Parker, Frank A., 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Isolationists, 1940-1941; Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Macomb- Madrid- Morristown, 1940-1941; 1943 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Dairy Farmers Union, 1940-1942 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Albany Officials & Departments, 1940-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Buffalo, 1940-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Clubs--Organizations, 1940-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Jefferson County, 1940-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Kellock--Grace, Jean and Mabel, 1940-1942; Undated (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Messena, 1940-1943 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Ogdensburg, 1940-1943 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Senate, 1940-1943 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Hanley, Joe, 1940-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Congratulations, 1940; 1942; Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1940 Report of the Joint Legislative Committee on Home Rule for Villages, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - C.S. Church Decorating--Cornelius Webster, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hammond- Hermon- Hopkinton, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Senate Bills Introduced by Graves, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Amendment to the Federal State Order (Milk), 1941; Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Edwards, 1941-1942 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Franklin County, 1941-1942; 1945; Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - New York City, 1941-1943 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cowan, Rita M., 1941-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Economy Commission (1 of 2), 1941-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Economy Commission (2 of 2), 1941-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - McMasters, Norman, 1941-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Help From RFG, 1941; 1944; Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Campaign and Personal Correspondence, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Conservation, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lynn Gordon Appel: Inquires and Paperwork, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Senate Bills, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Department of Audit and Control and Governors Portrait Committee, 1942; Undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Brasher Falls, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Buffalo: Claim Bill (Letters), 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Commissioner--Out of District, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Piercefield, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Resolutions--Out of District, 1942-1943 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Canton, 1942-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Political Correspondence, 1942-1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Legislative Correspondence Including the "Little Byrd Bill", 1942-1945; Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Albany, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Burt Donaldson in Prison, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Erminie Traxel, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - G.O.P. State and Local Campaigns, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Gouverneur, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hammond- Hermon- Hopkinton, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Lawrence-Lisbon-Louisville, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Milk Publicity, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Milk Publicity, 1943 (Flat-file 6)
  - Morristown- Madrid, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Requests, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Rochester, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Senate Bills Introduced by Graves, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Franklin County, 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Massena, 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - New York, 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Ogdensburg, 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Potsdam, 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Washington, D.C., 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Winthrop, N.Y., 1943; Undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Campaign--National, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Cities Aside From Ogdensburg-Rochester-Syracuse, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Members, Officers and Standing Committees, 1943; 1948 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Economy Commission, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Investigation, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    May be connected to folder titled "Handwritten Senate Notes and Supplemental Material."
  - Legislative, Political and Personal Correspondence, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - NY State Economy Commission Preliminary Report, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Suggestions to New York Farmers on Making Income-Tax Returns, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Education, 1944; Undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Hammond-Hermon-Hopkinton, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Macomb-Morristown-Madrid-Norfolk, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - New York, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Proceedings of the Board of Supervisors and Amendment on Supervisors in St. Lawrence County, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Political and Legislative Correspondence, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Canton, 1944-1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Political, Legislative and Personal Correspondence, 1944-1946; Undated (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Agriculture and Cattle, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Albany Officials--Letters, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Creation of Commission Against Discrimination: Intro 833 Pr. 1138, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Entry, Inspection and Investigation: Intro 115 Pr. 115, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Authority for Power Authority to Print Additional Copies 13th Annual Report: Intro 1967 Pr. 2316, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Canton, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Economy Commission, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Edwards, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Eliminating the Requirement of Reports of Receipts and Disbursements for State Fair Purposes: Intro 1132 Pr 1209, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Fine--Fowler, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Frozen Desserts: Intro 421 Pr 422, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Gouverneur, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Grange, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Incorporate the Roman Catholic Diocese of Ogdensburg: Intro 1634 Pr 1820, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Jefferson County, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Labeling in Relation to Olive Oil Mixtures: Intro 136 Pr 976, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lawrence-Lisbon-Louisville, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Massena, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Motor Vehicle Registration: Intro 1527 Pr. 1672, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Norwood and Norfolk, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Oleo Margarine Extension: Intro 365 Pr 366, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Postwar Planning for Milk--Booklet, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Preliminary Report for Northwest Adirondack Magnetite District, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Recording Certificates of Honorable Discharges of War Veterans: Intro 195 Pr. 685, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Senate Bills and Pay Voucher From, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Soldiers, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Taking Minerals in the Forest Preserve: Intro 855 Pr 831, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Vitamin and Bread to Have Specific Vitamin and Mineral Contents: Intro 650 Pr 836, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Potsdam, 1945; Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Assorted Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Gouverneur, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Jefferson County, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Letters Written by Paul D. Graves, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Messena, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Soldiers, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Waddington, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Berghold & Others, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bill: $50 Damages Before Filing A Report and Correspondence, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Franklin County, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Potsdam, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Political, Legislative and Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Agricultural Bulletin: List of Milk Dealers and Milk Plants in New York State, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Bill Relating to Ogdensburg, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Bill Relating to Vehicles, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Bills on Agriculture, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Bills Relating to Election Law, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Deputy Clerks and Defining Their Powers and Duties, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Digest of 1946 Laws (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Dogs Killing Deer Within State Parks, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Hammond-Hermon-Hopkinton, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Invitations, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Lawrence-Lisbon-Louisville, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Letter Supporting Milk Legislation In and Out of District, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Macomb-Morristown-Madrid-Norfolk, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Milk Inspection: Releases, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - New York School for the Deaf, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Ogdensburg, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Releases, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Trapping Season: Intro 1937 Pr. 2180 and Correspondence, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Deferred Registration--Revised, 1946; Undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Norwood, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Reference File for Teachers Salaries From New York Teachers' Interest Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Reference File for Teachers Salaries From New York Teachers' Interest Committee, 1946-1947 (Flat-file 7)
  - State Publications, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Thank You Letters, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Charter: City of Ogdensburg, 1946-1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Memorandums, 1946-1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Potsdam, 1946-1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - State Aid for Teachers and Schools (1 of 2), 1946-1948; Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - State Aid for Teachers and Schools (2 of 2), 1946-1948; Undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - 3/4 Registration Year License Bill, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Agricultural Committee, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Amend Agriculture and Market Law, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - An Act to Amend the City Charter of Ogdensburg, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - App. 2,000,000 for Indemnity--Diseases of Cattle--Same As Used For T.B. Bill, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - App. $25,000 Census Bill: Mastitis, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Appearance of Whiskey Glasses, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Bargaining Agencies, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Bargaining Agencies, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Change Date Dog Enumerations From January to November--16th of Any Given Year, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Cranberry Lake Bill, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Entry, Inspection and Investigation: Intro 482 Pr. 495, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Exempting Cities From the Licensing Requirements Governing the Sale of Milk, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Fertilizers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Franklin County, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Franklin County Teachers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Granting and Revoking Licenses to Milk Dealers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Historical Chronology on the St. Lawrence Project, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Incorporating in a Single Text Changes Made by Two Separate Amendments, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Labeling of Agricultural Seeds, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Marking of Thread, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Marking Milk Bottles, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Method of Sale of Lawn Dressing and Fertilizers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Milk Control Powers of the Commissioner of Agriculture During A Public Emergency, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Milk Inspection, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Mortgages Reference Tax Sale Property, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Notice of Increased Assessment in Towns in Franklin County, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Notice Increased Assessments in Towns of St. Lawrence County, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Ogdensburg Bill Relating to the Levy of Taxes: General Purpose by Common Council, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Private Owned Kennel Dogs, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Records and Uniform System of Cost Kept by Milk Dealers, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Repeal Chapter 155 of the Laws of 1946, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Repeal Section 258-M-Limit Voting Law, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Sale of Fuelwood, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Sale, Transportation of Insecticides and Poisons, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Standard Weights of Containers for Flour and Meals, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - St. Lawrence County Legislative Correspondence, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Term "Processing Plant": Agriculture and Markets, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Weighing Milk and Cream, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Wrapping Loose Candy and Confectionery Bars, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Franklin County Teachers, 1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Messena: Teachers and Others, 1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Ogdensburg: Station Employees & Others, 1947; Undated (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Political, Legislative and Personal Correspondence, 1947-1948; Undated (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Amend Law Re: Entry, Inspection & Investigation, Agriculture & Market, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Amend State Aid for T.B.-- Franklin County, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Amending A & M Law in Relation to Powers of the Commission, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Amending A & M Law in Relation to Transportation of Bees & Bee Material, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Appraisal of Damages Done to Domestic Animals By Dogs, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Bonds Filled By Milk Dealers, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Buttering and Substitutes: State Inspection, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Children's Camps in New York State Booklet, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Compensation of Assessors for Service Rendered Damages to Domestic Animals Done By Dogs, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Cooperative Voting, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Cranberry Bill, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Dust Diseases (Silicosis)--Compensation & State Aid, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Economic Poisons, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Fees For Dog Enumerators, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Institution Farms, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Kennels of Pure Bred Dogs, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Lateral Sewers in Villages and Costs, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - License Auction Rings, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Limitations of Milk Control, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - McKinney's New York Session Law Service--17th Session, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Messena Housing Authority, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Milk Control, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Milk Dealers License, Granting and Revoking, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Ogdensburg Tax, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Olive Oil Mixtures, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Power of Local Authorities: Respect to Traffic, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Refrigerated Warehouse and Locker Plants, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Repeal Act 2-A of the A&M Law: Division of the State Fair, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Repeal Sect. 59-60-61-62 of A&M Law Relating to Manufacture and Sale, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Repeal Unit Voting--Cooperative Corporations, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Sale and Analysis of Concentrated Commercial Feeding Stuffs, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Sale of Bread, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Slaughtering of Animals With Tuberculosis, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Social Welfare: Care of Persons With Tuberculosis, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Suspension of Licenses and Certificates: Motor Vehicle, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - System of Cost Accounting to be Kept by Milk Dealer, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Tattooing Dogs, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Repeal Section 258-M, 1948; Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bills and Amendments, 1948; Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Analysis of Senate Bills, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Brasher (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Canton (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, Speeches and Acts, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Depeyster (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Hammond (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hoover and Curtis Women's Club, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Lawrence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - List of Names by Town, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Macomb (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Messena (List of Names), Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Milk [Dairy Testing Course Description], Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Mining in the Adirondacks and Catskill Parks, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Radio, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - RFG Senate Campaign Postcards, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Speeches, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - State of New York Summary of Expenditures, Personal and Debts for Certain Years, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Written List of Legislative Acts with 'For' and 'Against' Marks, Undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Subject Files, 1911-1948; 3; 2.79 cubic ft.
  This series mainly contains materials of Graves' activities that were outside of her duties as a public official. Although her personal files were often interfiled with her professional records the materials in this series were clearly distinct and therefore kept separate. Included are documents of house renovations, papers from her sons and husband, keepsakes, pamphlets, invitations and letters from the many social and civic organizations Graves was a member of, including material from the Daughters of the American Revolution. Also contains stamps of Graves' image and political pins.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Buttons and Medals, 1925; 1939; Undated (Artifact-box 1)
  - DAR Anti-Communist Materials (1 of 2), 1927-1928; 1930-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - DAR Anti-Communist Materials (2 of 2), 1927-1928; 1930-1934; Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DAR Historical Markers, 1929; Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution (1 of 2), 1912-1944; Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution (2 of 2), 1912-1944; Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution: Membership Verification, 1911; 1913-1914; Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution: Ribbons, 1922-1924; 1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Diary of Mrs. Donas: Entries About Time Spent in RFG Office, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dog Inquiries and Dog License, 1937; 1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Condolences (Mother), 1940; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Graves, Marcus, 1918; 1923; 1931-1932; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Graves, Marcus, 1927-1930; 1932; 1934-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Graves, Marcus--Letters, 1943-1944; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Graves, Marcus--Letters, 1944-1945; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Graves, Paul, 1918; 1921; 1923-1926; 1930; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Graves, Perle, 1934-1938; 1944; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - House Renovations, 1937-1938; 1941-1942; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Invitations (1 of 2), 1917; 1925-1930; 1932; 1935-1936; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Invitations (2 of 2), 1917; 1925-1930; 1932; 1935-1936; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Keepsakes, 1933; 1940; Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Letter From Rhoda to Perle, 1930; 1938 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Martha Washington Republican Club, 1932; 1934; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - New York State Journal, 1942-1948 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Republican Bulletin, 1920 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Rural New Yorker, 1936; 1943-1944; 1946-1948 (Oversized 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1948 (Oversized 3)
  - Scrapbooks, 1946-1947 (Oversized 4)
  - The Shakespeare Club, 1917-1920; 1922-1925; 1929 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Stamp and Seal, Undated (Artifact-box 2)
  - Stamps of RFG, Undated (Artifact-box 3)
  - Taxes, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Taxes, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Women Republican, 1920 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Women's Club and Other Organizations, 1916-1920; 1922-1923; 1925; 1928; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)